<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Block>
  <Text ID="0">{C1}The Pokémon can send nearby enemies to sleep.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="1">{C1}The Pokémon can send nearby enemies to sleep for a long time.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="2">{C1}Reduces nearby enemies' Attack.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="3">{C1}Reduces nearby enemies' Speed.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="4">{C1}Reduces nearby enemies' accuracy.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="5">{C1}Increases nearby allies' Energy.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="6">{C1}Increases nearby allies' Defense.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="7">{C1}The Pokémon is able to collect more gold.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="8">{C1}The Pokémon is able to collect considerably more gold.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="9">{C1}The Pokémon explodes upon fainting, inflicting damage on those nearby.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="a">{C1}Appears disguised as an allied Pokémon.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="b">{C1}The Pokémon has several different Abilities and can inflict damage upon Pokémon of all types.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="c">{C1}The Pokémon benefits from allied Warrior Skills, wherever they are.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="d">{C1}Enemies adjacent to the Pokémon cannot move.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="e">{C1}Enables a Pokémon to chop down trees with their attacks.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="f">{C1}Enables a Pokémon to smash rocks with their attacks.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="10">{C1}Increases Range when there are no other Pokémon within three squares.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="11">{C1}Increases Range.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="12">{C1}Forces hit enemies to switch places with adjacent enemies.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="13">{C1}Raises Attack when the Pokémon is above its target.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="14">{C1}Raises Attack when the Pokémon is below its target.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="15">{C1}Boosts the effectiveness of adjacent allies' Fire-type attacks.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="16">{C1}Boosts the effectiveness of adjacent allies' Water-type attacks.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="17">{C1}Raises Attack in proportion to distance moved.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="18">{C1}Improves stats every time the Pokémon defeats an enemy.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="19">{C1}Reduces Range of hit enemies.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="1a">{C1}The Pokémon can act as a decoy, attracting enemy attacks.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="1b">{C1}The Pokémon can act as a decoy, protecting allies from enemy moves.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="1c">{C1}The Pokémon can move freely through squares that contain allies.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="1d">{C1}The Pokémon can restore a used Warrior Skill when their army is struggling.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="1e">{C1}Improves stats when surrounded by enemies.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="1f">{C1}Adjacent enemies can move only one square.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="20">{C1}The user just flops and splashes around to no effect at all... {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="21">{C1}The target is physically pounded with a long tail or a foreleg, etc. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="22">{C1}A physical attack in which the user charges and slams into the target with its whole body. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="23">{C1}The target is slapped repeatedly, back and forth, two to five times in a row.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="24">{C1}The target is raked with sharp claws or scythes two to five times in quick succession. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="25">{C1}The user lunges at the target at a speed that makes it almost invisible.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="26">{C1}The user sticks out its head and attacks by charging straight into the target. It may also make the target flinch.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="27">{C1}The user attacks by striking the target with its hard tail. It hits the Pokémon two to five times in a row. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="28">{C1}The user drops onto the target with its full body weight. It may also leave the target with paralysis. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="29">{C1}The user bites hard on the target with its sharp front fangs. It may also make the target flinch.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="2a">{C1}The target is attacked with a slash of claws, etc. It has a high critical-hit ratio.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="2b">{C1}The user lets loose a horribly echoing shout with the power to inflict damage.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="2c">{C1}The user releases countless shots of light.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="2d">{C1}The target is attacked with small flames. It may also leave the target with a burn.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="2e">{C1}The user bites with flame-cloaked fangs. It may also make the target flinch or leave it burned.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="2f">{C1}The user cloaks itself in fire and charges at the target. It may also leave the target with a burn.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="30">{C1}The user attacks the target with a bursting flame.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="31">{C1}The user slams its target with its flame-covered body.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="32">{C1}The target becomes trapped within a fierce vortex of fire that hits them four to five times.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="33">{C1}The target is scorched with an intense blast of fire. It may also leave the target with a burn.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="34">{C1}Cloaked in flames, the user dances and flaps its wings. It may also raise the user's Attack.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="35">{C1}The target is attacked with an intense blast of all-consuming fire. It may also leave the target with a burn. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="36">{C1}The user attacks by engulfing the target in an intense, yet beautiful, blue flame. It may leave the target with a burn. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="37">{C1}The user attacks the target with fire. If the target is holding an item, the item becomes burnt up and unusable.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="38">{C1}A spray of countless bubbles is jetted at the target. It may also lower the target's Speed.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="39">{C1}The enemy is blasted with a forceful shot of water.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="3a">{C1}A spray of bubbles is forcefully ejected at the target. It may also lower the target's Speed.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="3b">{C1}If the target's HP is down to about half, this attack will hit with double the power. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="3c">{C1}A pulse of water is ejected at the target, confusing them.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="3d">{C1}The user attacks by swinging its tail as if it were a vicious wave in a raging storm.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="3e">{C1}The target is blasted by a huge volume of water launched under great pressure.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="3f">{C1}Shock the target, with a potential to inflict paralysis.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="40">{C1}The user hurls an electric orb at the target. The faster the user is than the target, the greater the damage. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="41">{C1}Charge the target while shrouded in electricity, with a potential to inflict paralysis. The user is weakened for 1 turn.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="42">{C1}A flare of electricity is loosed to strike the area around the user. It may also cause paralysis. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="43">{C1}A strong electric blast is loosed at the target. It may also leave the target with paralysis. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="44">{C1}After making its attack, the user will switch places with another Pokémon.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="45">{C1}Strike the target with an enormous lightning bolt. It may also cause paralysis.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="46">{C1}Charge the target while shrouded in electricity, with a potential to inflict paralysis. The user is weakened for 1 turn.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="47">{C1}The user charges at its target, surrounding itself with a great amount of electricity. It may leave the target with paralysis. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="48">{C1}A nutrient-draining attack. The user's HP is restored by half the damage taken by the target.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="49">{C1}The enemy is struck with slender, whiplike vines to inflict damage.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="4a">{C1}A nutrient-draining attack. The user's HP is restored by half the damage taken by the target. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="4b">{C1}The target is slashed with a sharp leaf. It has a high critical-hit ratio.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="4c">{C1}A sharp-edged leaf is launched to slash at the target. It has a high critical-hit ratio. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="4d">{C1}Petals are scattered two to three times to attack the target. The user is temporarily immobilized.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="4e">{C1}A storm of sharp leaves is whipped up. The move's recoil lowers the user's Attack. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="4f">{C1}Create a small blizzard that may also freeze the target.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="50">{C1}Blow an icy gale toward the target. May also reduce the target's Range.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="51">{C1}The target is struck with an icy-cold beam of energy. It may also freeze the target solid. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="52">{C1}The user continually rolls into the target several times. It becomes stronger each time it hits. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="53">{C1}The user attacks by harshly dropping an icicle onto the target. It may also make the target flinch. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="54">{C1}A howling blizzard is summoned to strike the opposing team. It may also freeze them solid. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="55">{C1}The target is attacked with a sharp chop. Critical hits land more easily.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="56">{C1}The target is attacked with a shock wave. It may also leave the target with paralysis. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="57">{C1}This attack inflicts great damage on a sleeping target. It also wakes the target up, however. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="58">{C1}The target is attacked with a knee kick from a jump. If it misses, the user is hurt instead. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="59">{C1}The user looses a blast of aura power from deep within its body at the target. This move is certain to hit. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="5a">{C1}The user delivers a double chop with its forearms crossed. Critical hits land more easily.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="5b">{C1}Attack with tremendous force. The user's Attack and Defense will decrease as a result. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="5c">{C1}The user attacks by slicing with its long horns. The target's stat changes don't affect this attack's damage. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="5d">{C1}Sting the enemy with a poisoned needle. May poison the target.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="5e">{C1}An attack with a high critical-hit ratio. This tail attack may also poison the target.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="5f">{C1}The user bites the enemy with toxic fangs. It may also leave the target badly poisoned. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="60">{C1}A slashing attack with a poisonous blade that may also leave the target poisoned. Critical hits land more easily.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="61">{C1}Unsanitary sludge is hurled at the target. It may also poison the target.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="62">{C1}The target is stabbed with a tentacle or arm steeped in poison. It may also poison the target.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="63">{C1}The user drenches the target in a special poisonous liquid. Its power is doubled if the target is poisoned.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="64">{C1}The user slaps dirt at the target, dealing damage and lowering the opponent's accuracy. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="65">{C1}The user stomps down on the ground and attacks everything in the area. Hit Pokémon's Speed is reduced. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="66">{C1}The user throws a blob of mud at the target, which may lower accuracy. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="67">{C1}The attacker digs underground in the first turn then pops up in the next turn to attack.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="68">{C1}The user crashes into its target while rotating its body like a drill. Critical hits land more easily. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="69">{C1}The user makes the ground under the target erupt with power. It may also lower the target's Defense.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="6a">{C1}The target is struck with large, imposing wings spread wide to inflict damage.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="6b">{C1}The user takes the target into the sky then drops it during the next turn. The target cannot attack while in the sky. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="6c">{C1}The user tucks in its wings and charges from a low altitude. The user is weakened for 1 turn.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="6d">{C1}The target is hit by a weak telekinetic force. It may also leave the target confused. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="6e">{C1}Teleport to another square.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="6f">{C1}Emit a beam of mysterious light in the enemy's direction. It may leave the target confused.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="70">{C1}The user employs hypnotic suggestion to make the target fall into a deep sleep. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="71">{C1}The user eats the dreams of a sleeping target. It absorbs half the damage caused to heal the user's HP. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="72">{C1}The user materializes an odd psychic wave to attack the target. This attack does physical damage. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="73">{C1}The user tears at the target with blades formed by psychic power. It has a high critical-hit ratio. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="74">{C1}The user launches a strong psychokinetic attack, lowering their enemy's Defense. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="75">{C1}A hunk of psychic energy attacks the target 2 turns after this move is used.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="76">{C1}The user materializes an odd psychic wave to attack the target. This attack does physical damage. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="77">{C1}The user bites the target. If the target is holding an item, the user eats it and gains its effect. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="78">{C1}The target is slashed with scythes or claws. Its power increases if it hits in succession.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="79">{C1}The user slashes at the target by crossing its scythes or claws as if they were a pair of scissors.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="7a">{C1}The enemy is stabbed twice by a pair of stingers. It may also poison the target.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="7b">{C1}The target is attacked with rocks thrown forcefully two to five times in a row. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="7c">{C1}Bombard the enemy with rocks. It may also reduce the target's Range.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="7d">{C1}Send large rocks crashing into the enemy. It may also cause the target to flinch.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="7e">{C1}The user stabs the target with a sharpened stone. It has a high critical-hit ratio.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="7f">{C1}The user launches a huge boulder at the enemy to attack. Cannot be used 2 turns in a row.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="80">{C1}Aggressively lick the enemy. It may also cause the target to flinch. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="81">{C1}The user attacks the target while shouting in a startling fashion. It may also make the target flinch. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="82">{C1}This relentless attack does massive damage to a target affected by status problems.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="83">{C1}The user extends its shadow and attacks the enemy from behind.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="84">{C1}Attack the enemy with a ball of dark shadows, lowering the enemy's Defense. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="85">{C1}This attack hits the target with a shock wave of pure rage. This attack always inflicts 40 HP damage. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="86">{C1}The user slashes the target with huge, sharp claws. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="87">{C1}The user knocks away the target, causing it to be switched out for a different Pokémon.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="88">{C1}The target is attacked with a shock wave generated by the user's gaping mouth.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="89">{C1}The user tackles the target while exhibiting overwhelming menace. It may also make the target flinch.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="8a">{C1}The user blasts the enemy with power that distorts even time. It cannot be used 2 turns in a row.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="8b">{C1}The user rampages and attacks two to three times. The user is temporarily immobilized.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="8c">{C1}The user approaches the target disarmingly then throws a sucker punch. It hits without fail. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="8d">{C1}If the target has already taken some damage in the same turn, this attack's power is doubled.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="8e">{C1}The target is bitten with viciously sharp fangs. It may make the target flinch.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="8f">{C1}The user turns the target's power against it. The higher the target's Attack stat, the greater the damage. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="90">{C1}Slash the target while its attention is diverted. It has a high critical-hit ratio.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="91">{C1}The user crunches up the target with sharp fangs. It may also lower the target's Defense stat.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="92">{C1}The user lets loose a pitch-black shock wave at its target. It may also lower the target's accuracy.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="93">{C1}Scratch the enemy with steel claws. It may also increase the user's Attack.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="94">{C1}Strike the enemy with a hard head. It may also cause the target to flinch.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="95">{C1}Beat the enemy with a hardened tail. It may also lower the target's Attack.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="96">{C1}The target is hit with a hard punch fired like a meteor. It may also raise the user's Attack. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="97">{C1}The user tackles the target with a high-speed spin. The slower the user, the greater the damage.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="98">{C1}The user strikes the target with tough punches as fast as bullets. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="99">{C1}The user gathers all its light energy and releases it at once. It may also lower the target's Defense.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="9a">{C1}Unleash a powerful kick to knock the enemy off their feet.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="9b">{C1}Raises Attack (for 3 turns). {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="9c">{C1}Raises Defense (for 3 turns). {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="9d">{C1}Significantly increases Range.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="9e">{C1}Raises Attack of Warrior's Pokémon and adjacent allies (for 3 turns).{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="9f">{C1}Increases Range of Warrior's Pokémon and adjacent allies.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="a0">{C1}Restores HP of all allied Pokémon.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="a1">{C1}Significantly raises Attack.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="a2">{C1}Raises Defense of Warrior's Pokémon and adjacent allies (for 3 turns).{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="a3">{C1}Improves accuracy (for 3 turns).{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="a4">{C1}All moves are guaranteed to hit.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="a5">{C1}Improves accuracy and increases chance of critical hits (for 3 turns).{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="a6">{C1}Enables Warrior's Pokémon to climb to high places.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="a7">{C1}Increases probability of inflicting status ailments on enemies (for 3 turns).{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="a8">{C1}Makes enemies flinch (for 3 turns).{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="a9">{C1}Increases Range and makes enemies flinch.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="aa">{C1}Restores HP of Warrior's Pokémon and adjacent allies.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="ab">{C1}Restores HP. Cannot move for 3 turns.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="ac">{C1}Slowly restores HP of Warrior's Pokémon and adjacent allies (for 3 turns).{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="ad">{C1}Cures status ailments of Warrior's Pokémon and adjacent allies.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="ae">{C1}Cures any allied Pokémon who are poisoned or paralyzed.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="af">{C1}Cures any allied Pokémon who are confused or sleeping.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="b0">{C1}Cures any allied Pokémon who are burned or frozen.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="b1">{C1}Two treasure boxes will appear upon defeating an enemy. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="b2">{C1}Significantly increases Range and Attack.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="b3">{C1}Raises Attack and allows Warrior's Pokémon to move twice.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="b4">{C1}Allows Warrior's Pokémon to move twice.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="b5">{C1}Makes enemies flinch and allows Warrior's Pokémon to move twice.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="b6">{C1}Cures status ailments and restores HP for all allied Pokémon.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="b7">{C1}Two treasure boxes will appear upon defeating an enemy. Increases Energy (for 3 turns).{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="b8">{C1}Two treasure boxes will appear upon defeating an enemy. Increases Energy and Attack (for 3 turns).{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="b9">{C1}Improves accuracy and increases chance of critical hits for Warrior's Pokémon and adjacent allies.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="ba">{C1}Increases Range and Attack for all allied Pokémon.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="bb">{C1}Blocks enemy critical hits and increases Speed for all allied Pokémon (for 3 turns).{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="bc">{C1}Increases Speed and ensures all moves hit (for 3 turns).{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="bd">{C1}Raises Attack but lowers Defense of Warrior's Pokémon and adjacent allies.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="be">{C1}Enables Warrior's Pokémon to avoid all enemy moves.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="bf">{C1}Increases Attack and Defense of all allied Pokémon (for 3 turns).{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="c0">{C1}Increases Range of Warrior's Pokémon and adjacent allies (for 3 turns).{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="c1">{C1}Increases Attack and Range of all allied Pokémon (for 3 turns).{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="c2">{C1}Restores HP of Warrior's Pokémon and adjacent allies―at a cost...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="c3">{C1}Blocks enemy critical hits and increases Energy for all allied Pokémon.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="c4">{C1}Increases effectiveness of moves against Pokémon with male Warrior partners (for 3 turns). {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="c5">{C1}Increases Range, makes enemies flinch, and allows Warrior's Pokémon to climb to high places (for 3 turns).{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="c6">{C1}Dramatically improves Defense (for 3 turns).{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="c7">{C1}Blocks enemy critical hits and status ailments for all allied Pokémon (for 3 turns).{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="c8">{C1}Disables all enemy Warrior Skills.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="c9">{C1}Increases Attack and Range of all allied Pokémon.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="ca">{C1}All allies' moves will have a chance to confuse the enemy.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="cb">{C1}Increases Range, allows Warrior's Pokémon to climb to high places, and increases chance of critical hits (for 3 turns).{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="cc">{C1}Improves Speed, allows Warrior's Pokémon to climb to high places, and increases chance of critical hits (for 3 turns).{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="cd">{C1}Increases chance of critical hits and allows the Warrior's Pokémon to move twice.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="ce">{C1}Raises Attack in proportion to the number of female Warriors on the battlefield.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="cf">{C1}Raises Attack and restores HP of Warrior's Pokémon and adjacent allies.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="d0">{C1}Raises Defense and restores HP of Warrior's Pokémon and adjacent allies.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="d1">{C1}Improves Speed and makes enemies flinch.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="d2">{C1}Raises Energy and Attack of all allied Pokémon.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="d3">{C1}All allies' moves will be successful (for 3 turns).{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="d4">{C1}Raises Attack and Defense (for 4 turns).{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="d5">{C1}Increases Range, and attacks will always be successful (for 3 turns).{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="d6">{C1}Raises Attack and makes enemies flinch (for 4 turns). {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="d7">{C1}Increases Speed, and attacks will always be successful (for 3 turns). {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="d8">{C1}Raises Defense and blocks status ailments (for 3 turns). {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="d9">{C1}Increases Range and Attack. Reduces HP to 1.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="da">{C1}Restores 20 HP. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="db">{C1}Restores 50 HP. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="dc">{C1}Restores 200 HP. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="dd">{C1}Fully restores HP.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="de">{C1}Restores HP and cures status ailments.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="df">{C1}Restores HP when standing on grass (for 3 turns).{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="e0">{C1}Restores HP when standing in water (for 3 turns).{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="e1">{C1}Restores HP when standing in magma (for 3 turns).{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="e2">{C1}Restores HP when standing in a poison bog (for 3 turns).{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="e3">{C1}Restores HP when standing on rock (for 3 turns).{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="e4">{C1}Restores HP when standing on snow or ice (for 3 turns).{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="e5">{C1}Cures paralysis.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="e6">{C1}Cures sleep.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="e7">{C1}Cures poisoning.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="e8">{C1}Cures burning.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="e9">{C1}Cures freezing.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="ea">{C1}Cures all status ailments. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="eb">{C1}Prevents paralysis (for 3 turns).{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="ec">{C1}Prevents sleep (for 3 turns).{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="ed">{C1}Prevents poisoning (for 3 turns).{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="ee">{C1}Prevents burning (for 3 turns).{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="ef">{C1}Prevents freezing (for 3 turns).{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="f0">{C1}Prevents any status ailments (for 3 turns).{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="f1">{C1}Slightly increases Energy.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="f2">{C1}Increases Energy. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="f3">{C1}Significantly increases Energy. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="f4">{C1}Increases Energy to maximum level. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="f5">{C1}Slightly increases the probability of linking with Pokémon (for 3 turns). {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="f6">{C1}Increases the probability of linking with Pokémon (for 4 turns). {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="f7">{C1}Significantly increases the probability of linking with Pokémon (for 5 turns). {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="f8">{C1}Guarantees a critical hit on the next attack.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="f9">{C1}Increases Range by one square (for 3 turns). {End}</Text>
</Block>