<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Block>
  <Text ID="0">{C1}A young Warrior of Avia prepares to take to the sky. His quest: the unification of Ransei...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="1">{C1}Motonari desires nothing more than to devote his days to Pokémon research, but the world just won't let him be...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="2">{C1}Entrusted with Nō's castle, Okuni thinks that this might be the ideal opportunity to find the man of her dreams. However...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="3">{C1}The tale of how Magoichi stumbled into the role of leader without really meaning to. If only he could keep his eyes on the prize...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="4">{C1}“Ransei's Greatest Beauty... Now that's just gotta be me, hasn't it?!” Confident as ever, Kai steps boldly forth into a showdown between the greatest women Warriors of Ransei.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="5">{C1}The tale of three good friends who became embroiled in a trivial argument. Who could have known where it would lead...?{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="6">{C1}Ranmaru somehow finds himself caught up in the contest to decide Ransei's Greatest Beauty. If only someone would listen to him...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="7">{C1}“Even a drifter like me can't leave people stranded." The free-spirited Keiji decides to stand up for the downtrodden...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="8">{C1}The two living legends of Ransei... Rivals for so long, the time has finally come for them to stand together in battle...and fight!{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="9">{C1}The Legend of Ransei{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="a">{C1}The Road to Conquest{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="b">{C1}Happily Ever After{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="c">{C1}The Burden of Peace{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="d">{C1}The Way of the Warrior{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="e">{C1}The Joy of Battle{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="f">{C1}Pride and Precociousness{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="10">{C1}Tragic Determination{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="11">{C1}A Shroud of Darkness{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="12">{C1}Not Worth Fighting Over... 1{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="13">{C1}Teaching Them a Lesson{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="14">{C1}The Reluctant Genius{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="15">{C1}The Unparalleled Warrior{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="16">{C1}A Ninja amongst Ninjas{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="17">{C1}Archenemies{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="18">{C1}Time for Battle!{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="19">{C1}Land of Love and Righteousness{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="1a">{C1}Love is a Battlefield{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="1b">{C1}The Final Gamble{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="1c">{C1}Blowing in the Wind{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="1d">{C1}Ransei's Legendary Beauty{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="1e">{C1}All Grown Up{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="1f">{C1}The Rebel{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="20">{C1}That Which He Holds Dear{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="21">{C1}Not Worth Fighting Over... 2{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="22">{C1}The Rose of Ransei{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="23">{C1}The Visionary's Quest{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="24">{C1}Grace and Beauty{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="25">{C1}Pokémari and Me{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="26">{C1}The Dragon's Dream{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="27">{C1}Putting the Books Down{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="28">{C1}A Date with Destiny{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="29">{C1}This One Goes Out to My Fans{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="2a">{C1}Simply the Best{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="2b">{C1}Not Worth Fighting Over... 3{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="2c">{C1}A Fate Born of Beauty{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="2d">{C1}The Free Spirit's Path{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="2e">{C1}Two Heroes of Ransei{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="2f">{C1}Unknown{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="30">{C1}???{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="31">{C1}A youth in possession of a rare talent to communicate on a deep level with Pokémon of all kinds. This Warrior's friendship with Eevee dates back to childhood.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="32">{C1}A Warrior whose phenomenal strength surpasses all others. Renowned for showing no mercy in battle, he is feared by all who cross his path. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="33">{C1}A sweet, kindhearted young girl who is not without strength and resolve. By nature she is not drawn to battle but has nonetheless learned to embrace it when necessary.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="34">{C1}Behind the cheerful exterior of this Warrior lies an unusually sharp intelligence and a rare capacity to perceive things as they really are.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="35">{C1}His laid-back exterior hides a passionate nature that never shrinks from even the most fearsome opponents. Indeed, he is perpetually seeking out his next battle.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="36">{C1}Born to a clan famous for producing talented Warriors who fight alongside Electric-type Pokémon. Fiercely proud, she does not forgive easily. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="37">{C1}A reasonable and rational Warrior who shows exceptional tactical awareness in battle. His dream is to dedicate himself to the academic research of Pokémon.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="38">{C1}Never letting his composure slip for a second, his overly serene nature sometimes gets him into trouble. His loyalty to trusted friends, however, is unshakeable. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="39">{C1}A heroic and large-hearted type who loves nothing more than a good battle, particularly one where the chances of winning appear to be slim. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="3a">{C1}A gentle, peace-loving woman, adored and respected as a motherly figure by her allies.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="3b">{C1}Lively and mischievous, his self-confidence seems to know no bounds. Kenshin's lifelong rival.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="3c">{C1}Earnest and cheerful, with soaring ambitions that he refuses to let anyone dampen. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="3d">{C1}A veritable genius on the battlefield, he values nothing above the art of combat. Sworn enemies with Shingen and constantly looking for ways to overcome him.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="3e">{C1}Once a talented fighter, he now prefers to devote his energy to the game of Pokémari. A dandy with little knowledge of how the real world works, his naivety often lands him in trouble. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="3f">{C1}Despite his tendency to seem gruff and unaccommodating, he cares deeply for his allies. He has taken part in more battles than even he can count.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="40">{C1}An aloof and somewhat mysterious beauty who likes nothing more than watching talented Warriors in action on the battlefield. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="41">{C1}A ninja who seems set on throwing all of Ransei into turmoil. His true motivations for doing so, however, remain a mystery to all.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="42">{C1}A most magnanimous man who treats his allies with great affection and is venerated by them in return. Careful and patient, he achieves results one step at a time. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="43">{C1}A genius with truly astonishing brainpower and a confidence that doesn't quite fit his appearance, his dream is to spend every day sleeping. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="44">{C1}A firm believer that the end justifies the means, he is always focused on his current aim. He and Hanbei are close friends, united by their gifted natures.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="45">{C1}A capricious type who has the tendency to show off. When there's something he wants to get done, however, he has the talent to pull almost anything off. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="46">{C1}Mitsuhide's daughter is innocent and curious and cannot wait to learn more about the mysteries of the world. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="47">{C1}A ninja who believes that battle is no more than his duty. Extremely reticent, it is very rare for him to make his true feelings known. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="48">{C1}A mischievous prankster who is always teasing other people. Despite her constant fooling around, she displays remarkable skill as a ninja.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="49">{C1}A valiant young Warrior. Serious, with a strong sense of duty and justice, he is always focused on pursuing the path that he has determined for himself. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="4a">{C1}A sensible and uncomplicated Warrior who doesn't get hung up on trifles. He does, however, have a great love of women and will attempt to speak to any lady who passes his way.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="4b">{C1}Warmhearted and very dutiful, he will always attempt to punish anyone he feels has been unjust, in a bid to show them the true path.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="4c">{C1}Older sister of Kenshin, her heart is split between a kindly warmth and a strict discipline. Modest and refined, she never loses her cool. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="4d">{C1}A strong-willed girl who hates losing, she is in fact good hearted and caring toward others. Occasionally prone to fretting about her appearance.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="4e">{C1}Energetic and lighthearted, she is forever taking off at the drop of a hat and can be spotted in all four corners of Ransei.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="4f">{C1}A courageous and extremely talented Warrior. Earnest and very dutiful, he has no ambitions of his own but to serve his master.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="50">{C1}A famous Warrior, thought to be the strongest in all of Ransei. Valued as an ally, his enemies fear the day when they have to take him on. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="51">{C1}Tadakatsu's daughter is a dignified and composed Warrior who aspires to match her father's greatness and devotes herself wholeheartedly to achieving her aim.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="52">{C1}Stylish, with a love of interesting and unusual things, he has a tendency to drift from kingdom to kingdom. His talent as a Warrior, however, is not to be underestimated. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="53">{C1}Says exactly what is on his mind and therefore has a tendency to cause offense sometimes. He has a good head on him, however, and never forgets a favor done for him. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="54">{C1}Stubborn and very unwilling to change his own opinions. Often comes across as very sarcastic but is actually quite straightforward and pure hearted as a person. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="55">{C1}A simpleminded soul brimming over with pure macho energy. Often gets into trouble from not thinking things through properly but is also in possession of a determined streak. {End}</Text>
  <Text ID="56">{C1}{Char:0200}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="57">{C1}{Char:0200}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="58">{C1}{Char:0200}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="59">{C1}{Char:0200}{NameColor:33}{CharImage:30}{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="5a">{C1}{Char:9999}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}It doesn't look like {Name2}{C1} is able to link with {Poke}{C1}...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="5b">{C1}{Char:9999}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}It looks like {Name2}{C1} and {Poke}{C1} have warmed to each other a little.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="5c">{C1}{Char:9999}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}{Name2}{C1} has successfully linked with {Poke}{C1}...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="5d">{C1}{Char:9999}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}It looks like {Name2}{C1} and {Poke}{C1} have warmed to each other.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="5e">{C1}{Char:9999}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}It looks like {Name2}{C1} and {Poke}{C1} are much closer now!{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="5f">{C1}{Char:9999}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}{Name2}{C1} and {Poke}{C1} are really close now!{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="60">{C1}{Char:9999}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}{Name2}{C1} and {Poke}{C1} aren't as close as they were...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="61">{C1}{Char:9999}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}{Name2}{C1} and {Poke}{C1} did not warm to each other...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="62">{C1}{Char:9999}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}Watch as the linking lights flow toward you...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="63">{C1}{Char:9999}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}Press the button as soon as the linking lights reach the line!{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="64">{C1}{Char:9999}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}Warrior and Pokémon have warmed to each other a little.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="65">{C1}{Char:9999}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}The better your timing when you press that button, the closer the Pokémon and the Warrior will become...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="66">{C1}{Char:9999}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}When a Warrior becomes close enough to a Pokémon, they will form a link.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="67">{C1}{Char:9999}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}If you go on to win the battle, you can take these Pokémon with you.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="68">{C1}{Char:9999}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}Now then, let's try linking with {Poke}{C1}.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="69">{C1}{Char:9999}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}Stop on top of a {Color:32}banner{Color:33} to claim that {Color:32}banner{Color:33} for {Name}{C1}'s army.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="6a">{C1}{Char:9999}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}Claim all the {Color:32}banners{Color:33}, and {Color:32}victory{Color:33} is yours.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="6b">{C1}{Char:0002}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="6c">{C1}{Char:9999}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}If the enemy claims all the {Color:32}banners{Color:33}, then you will have been {Color:32}defeated{Color:33}.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="6d">{C1}{Char:0002}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="6e">{C1}{Char:0002}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="6f">{C1}{Char:9999}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}Your HP will be restored when you stop on top of a {Color:32}banner{Color:33}.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="70">{C1}{Char:9999}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}If your HP is getting low or if you're suffering from burns...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="71">{C1}{Char:9999}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}you can recover in a {Color:32}hot spring{Color:33}.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="72">{C1}{Char:0004}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}The spirit of the water gushes forth... Shall we sample some of it?{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="73">{C1}{Char:0002}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:34}Wh-What's going on?! There's water everywhere!{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="74">{C1}{Char:0004}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}What's your plan, {Name}{C1}?{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="75">{C1}{Char:0004}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}Defeat is only a matter of time unless you do something.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="76">{C1}{Char:9999}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}When the number of turns remaining reaches 0, the challenger loses the battle.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="77">{C1}{Char:0004}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="78">{C1}{Char:0004}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="79">{C1}{Char:0002}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="7a">{C1}{Char:0002}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="7b">{C1}{Char:0004}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}You wish to resist? Excellent.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="7c">{C1}{Char:0002}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="7d">{C1}{Char:0002}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:32}Now, if we could just close that {Color:32}flood gate{Color:33}...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="7e">{C1}{Char:0004}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:31}Can you feel it? There is something flowing down from the north... Something big...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="7f">{C1}{Char:0004}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:31}It's a wave... A crushing black wave...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="80">{C1}{Char:0004}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}But it will not sweep me away.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="81">{C1}{Char:0004}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}I will continue to fight, continue to cry out...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="82">{C1}{Char:0004}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:33}A bitter blow... But this is not over yet!{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="83">{C1}{Char:0076}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}I was born a Warrior, with the talent to communicate with Pokémon...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="84">{C1}{Char:0076}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}It is time to prove that I am worthy to stand on the field of battle!{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="85">{C1}{Char:0005}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}Our clan...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="86">{C1}{Char:0005}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}Famed throughout Ransei for our Electric-type Pokémon...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="87">{C1}{Char:0005}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}We built this place! It is a place in which to do battle!{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="88">{C1}{Char:0005}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:33}We did not intend it as a haven for the likes of you, {Name}{C1}!{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="89">{C1}{Char:0020}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}It looks like you drove {Color:30}Ginchiyo{Color:33} away.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="8a">{C1}{Char:0020}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}She does not take defeat lying down. She will return the favor soon, I am sure.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="8b">{C1}{Char:0020}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="8c">{C1}{Char:0002}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:34}So we're splitting up and going after those {Color:32}banners{Color:33}, right?{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="8d">{C1}{Char:0002}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:33}All right, |02,cc{C1}! We won't let you down!{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="8e">{C1}{Char:9999}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="8f">{C1}{Char:0006}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}What do you think it takes to win battles, {Name}{C1}?{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="90">{C1}{Char:0006}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}You're thinking...strength, right?{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="91">{C1}{Char:0006}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}But strength alone is not enough.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="92">{C1}{Char:0006}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}Do you understand what I'm saying? Doing battle is not just about defeating your enemies.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="93">{C1}{Char:0006}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:34}Your Pokémon, {Color:31}Eevee{Color:33}... It looks like you two have grown fairly close...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="94">{C1}{Char:0006}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}Hey, by the way, I read that there's some faraway world where people put Pokémon into these little balls and carry them around!{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="95">{C1}{Char:0006}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}Pretty strange, no? Now, where did I read that...?{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="96">{C1}{Char:0006}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="97">{C1}{Char:0006}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:32}I guess the peaceful days when I can just focus on my Pokémon research are still a long way away...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="98">{C1}{Char:0088}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}This battlefield is the very symbol of our fair kingdom of {Color:30}Greenleaf{Color:33}...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="99">{C1}{Char:0088}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}We who command Grass-type Pokémon shall not be defeated here!{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="9a">{C1}{Char:9999}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}{Color:32}Range{Color:33} is reduced on {Color:32}snowy{Color:33} terrain.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="9b">{C1}{Char:0007}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="9c">{C1}{Char:0007}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}I'm afraid I cannot allow you to disturb Lord {Color:30}Nobunaga{Color:33}.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="9d">{C1}{Char:0007}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:33}Here, on this battlefield...I will stop you!{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="9e">{C1}{Char:0021}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:33}And I'm here too! I hope you're ready!{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="9f">{C1}{Char:0021}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:33}I will defeat you, {Name}{C1}! For my father's sake!{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="a0">{C1}{Char:0008}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}The {Color:32}banners{Color:33} are at the {Color:32}ring's edge{Color:33}... You know what this means, don't you?{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="a1">{C1}{Char:0008}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}It's a gamble! Just like everything else in life...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="a2">{C1}{Char:9999}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}Those hit by attacks when at the {Color:32}ring's edge{Color:33} will fall down below.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="a3">{C1}{Char:0002}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="a4">{C1}{Char:0008}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="a5">{C1}{Char:9999}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="a6">{C1}{Char:0008}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="a7">{C1}{Char:0002}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="a8">{C1}{Char:0002}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="a9">{C1}{Char:0008}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}Looks like I'm at a disadvantage...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="aa">{C1}{Char:0008}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:31}But it wouldn't be any fun if the odds were in my favor!{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="ab">{C1}{Char:0008}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:31}Not knowing whether you're going to win or lose―that's the true thrill of the battlefield!{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="ac">{C1}{Char:0008}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="ad">{C1}{Char:0009}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}This is your first time on this battlefield, isn't it, {Name}{C1}?{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="ae">{C1}{Char:0009}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}Well, {Color:30}Viperia{Color:33} is full of ninjas...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="af">{C1}{Char:0009}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}You'll be amazed when you see all the tricks they've got!{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="b0">{C1}{Char:0010}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}A tower like this in the middle of the desert... Does it surprise you?{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="b1">{C1}{Char:0010}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}This is the tallest building in all of Ransei.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="b2">{C1}{Char:0010}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}Even Flying Pokémon would struggle to make it up here...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="b3">{C1}{Char:0010}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:31}You're welcome to try climbing it if you want, but I can't be held responsible for what might happen.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="b4">{C1}{Char:0010}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}Did I misread the situation...?{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="b5">{C1}{Char:0010}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}Still, the battle is far from over yet!{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="b6">{C1}{Char:0024}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}You are strong indeed. Just as I expected...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="b7">{C1}{Char:0024}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}You are a true Warrior, {Name}{C1}. There's no doubt about it!{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="b8">{C1}{Char:0011}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}Well, what do you think? Pretty nice view, huh?{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="b9">{C1}{Char:0011}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}It's my favorite battlefield in all of Ransei.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="ba">{C1}{Char:0011}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:33}And one day it's going to be me, not {Color:30}Nobunaga{Color:33}, who unites this region!{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="bb">{C1}{Char:0011}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}But not unless you start pulling your weight, {Color:30}Magoichi{Color:33}!{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="bc">{C1}{Char:0025}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:31}Okay, okay... Man, he's a terrible boss...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="bd">{C1}{Char:0012}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}I shall show my enemies the true meaning of battle...{Wait:30}20{Color:30}Kanetsugu{Color:33}!{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="be">{C1}{Char:0026}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:33}Yes, Lord {Color:30}Kenshin{Color:33}. Our enemies shall learn the true righteousness of our cause!{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="bf">{C1}{Char:0012}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:33}Their power is considerable... But they are no match for {Color:30}Kenshin{Color:33}!{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="c0">{C1}{Char:0027}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}Hehe... You seem to be enjoying yourself, Brother.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="c1">{C1}{Char:0027}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}But you should not make light of your enemies, {Color:30}Kenshin{Color:33}.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="c2">{C1}{Char:0027}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}If you believe you have justice on your side, you must prove it on the battlefield.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="c3">{C1}{Char:0002}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="c4">{C1}{Char:0013}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}This battlefield has been designed so that we might enjoy Pokémari as we fight!{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="c5">{C1}{Char:0013}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}Come, come! Let us begin, without further ado!{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="c6">{C1}{Char:0028}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}They're coming...!{Wait:30}20 Here we go!{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="c7">{C1}{Char:0014}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}What are you, frightened? You're never gonna win like that!{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="c8">{C1}{Char:0014}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}There's something I've got to protect... That's why I fight.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="c9">{C1}{Char:0014}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}So I'm sorry, but...I won't be holding back.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="ca">{C1}{Char:0014}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}Hm. This {Name}{C1} is the real thing...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="cb">{C1}{Char:0028}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}But we won't be defeated! Not here, in our kingdom!{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="cc">{C1}{Char:0014}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}Of course not. Come on, let's finish this off.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="cd">{C1}{Char:0015}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:31}Can you see it? That dancing flame, out on the battlefield?{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="ce">{C1}{Char:0015}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:31}It shines so brightly, it scorches the soul...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="cf">{C1}{Char:0015}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:31}Just like someone I know...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="d0">{C1}{Char:0029}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:30}Once this battle is over, I can carry on with my travels, right?{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="d1">{C1}{Char:0029}{NameColor:30}{CharImage:31}After all, I have places to go and people to meet!{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="d2">{C1}{Char:0001}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:31}Come, {Name}{C1}.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="d3">{C1}{Char:0001}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:31}Show that you are superior to {Color:30}Nobunaga{Color:33}. If you can...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="d4">{C1}{Char:0030}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:33}Lord {Color:30}Nobunaga{Color:33} must be protected!{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="d5">{C1}{Char:0030}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:33}I'm afraid I cannot make allowances for you, Lady {Color:31}Oichi{Color:33}!{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="d6">{C1}{Char:0016}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:31}I hope you're ready for some genuine hospitality...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="d7">{C1}{Char:0016}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:31}I'll show you things you can't see anywhere else...{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="d8">{C1}{Char:0016}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}No matter how much you struggle, people will continue to fight.{End}</Text>
  <Text ID="d9">{C1}{Char:0016}{NameColor:32}{CharImage:30}Stopping {Color:30}Nobunaga{Color:33} will not change the way of the world.{End}</Text>
</Block>